vineyardvines.com 2019-12-06

# FAQ's

## In-store Pick Up

To see if an item is eligible for In-Store Pickup, look for the In-Store Pickup option on the product detail page. Simply select the color, size and quantity and choose a store. 

I know you can’t wait to get your new items and we can’t wait to see you. We will email you as soon as your items are ready (within 4 hours) letting you know it’s time to pick up your order. If your order was placed after 2PM, you'll receive an email the following day.

Pick up is easy! All you need is your order confirmation email. 

Absolutely! That’s what friends are for. Just make sure they have your confirmation email with the order number. 

Whale yes you sure can! When you check out select Buy Online, Pickup In-Store for certain items, and select your preferred shipping method for your other items.

We understand sometimes things come up. You will receive and email once the product(s) is ready for pickup, then we will gladly hold your order for 72 hours. You will receive a cancellation email if you don't pick up the order within 72 hours. 

A hold is placed once you complete the order, but your card isn't charged until the items are picked up. 

Your payment will be authorized when you create your order and a hold will appear on your account, but you will not be charged until you pick up your order in the store. 

If you don't pick up your order within 72 hours, your order will be automatically canceled and you will not be charged for the items. Any hold that may have appeared on your card will be released.

We’re sorry to hear that you want to cancel your order. We would be more than happy to help! Just call the store you designated for pickup or customer care at 1-800-892-4982. 

To return or exchange your product(s), follow the steps outlined [here](https://www.vineyardvines.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-Vineyard-Vines-Site/default/OrderLocator-LoadOrderLocator).

You can also return your products in most of our [retail stores](http://www.vineyardvines.com/stores) excluding Mashpee, MA, Hamilton, Bermuda and any of our Outlet locations.

## Shipping

  * Street addresses, P.O. Boxes (please check box during checkout) and Military APO/FPO address
  * All 50 states including the District of Columbia (excluding all US Territories)
  * To select countries outside the US. 

The following items are not eligible for international shipping  
\- gift cards and e-gift cards  
\- promo and coupon codes  
\- gifting options (box, receipt and message)  
\- personalized items  
\- certain products that we're unable to ship outside the US (ties, bow ties, home, accessories, jewelry)

Shipping Costs are based on order merchandise total costs and the selected shipping method:

Merchandise Total | Standard Ground | Two-Day | Next Day  
---|---|---|---  
Please note that larger items, such as the Yeti Cooler, cost more to ship.  
$0-$50 | $8.50 | $18.50 | $26.50  
$50.01-$100 | $10 | $20 | $28  
$100.01-$124.99 | $12 | $22 | $30  
$125+ | FREE | $24 | $32  
  
We strive to process orders as quickly as we possibly can. Orders placed Monday through Friday are usually shipped within 48 hours. **Please note that during periods of high volume, it will take longer (sales, major promotions, Friends & Family, during the holidays, etc.)** Orders placed over the weekend are usually shipped the next business day. If you need your order to go out the same day you place it, please place your order before noon ET using an expedited service (excludes Saturday, Sunday and Holidays) and we’ll be sure to do our best to get you your merchandise in time.

Once processed, orders are shipped via Standard Ground (unless an expedited service is chosen). Standard Ground is delivered within 2-7 business days to most U.S. locations; however, we've found that orders will arrive even sooner than that.

Once an order has shipped, you will receive an email with tracking information. This email might wind up in your "Spam" email folder, so be sure to add vineyard vines to your "safe" list.

We apologize, but we cannot make changes, adjustments, or cancellations to an order after it has been submitted. We may still be able to help, though! Just give us a call at 800-892-4982.

Absolutely! When you set up your vineyard vines account, you’re able to enter separate shipping addresses and save addresses that you may want to ship to in the future.

You may have ordered a number of items that don’t fit into one box, or we are shipping your item from one of our store locations. You will receive an email with a tracking number and item list for each of your packages.

Please note, in order to fulfill your order to the best of our ability we sometimes ship your items directly from one of our stores which can result in multiple shipments for a single order. When this happens you may notice multiple posts to your credit card for a single order. The initial authorization is not a charge and will disappear from your account in a business day or so.

## Returns & Exchanges

To return or exchange your product(s), follow the steps outlined [here](https://www.vineyardvines.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-Vineyard-Vines-Site/default/OrderLocator-LoadOrderLocator).You can also return your products in most of our [retail stores](http://www.vineyardvines.com/stores) excluding Mashpee, MA, Hamilton, Bermuda and any of our Outlet locations.

To exchange your product, give us a call at 800-892-4982 and we will do our best to get your new products out to you quickly! You will be charged for the merchandise on its way to you (shipping is on us, of course), and you’ll be credited for your original purchase as soon as we receive your return.

Borderfree allows us to deliver our items to our international customers. When returning an international order you will be credited by Borderfree in the same currency and using the same exchange rate as your original tender. Returns must be made within 180 days of purchase. 

All European Union customers have a right to back out of a purchase within 7 days of completing the transaction (e.g. placing the order on the website). If a European Union customer cancels their order during this 7-day period, Borderfree will reimburse the customer for the cost of the product(s) AND any extra fees (i.e. shipping) paid by the customer to receive the item. Borderfree can, however, charge the customer for cost of shipping goods back to Borderfree. Reimbursement by Borderfree will be within 30 days.

Borderfree 525 Dell Road Carlstadt, NJ 07072 United States

Holiday gifts can be returned new, unused and with the garment tags still attached. We only accept returns for products purchased at vineyard vines stores or through the vineyard vines website or app. Regular priced items with in 60 days or sale items within 30 days of purchase can be issued a full refund to the purchasers credit card. After that time-frame your gift recipient can receive a gift card or store credit for their gift return. Have a Happy Holiday!

Items should be returned new, unused and with the garment tags still attached. We only accept returns for products purchased at vineyard vines stores or through the vineyard vines website or app. Underwear and swimwear should be tried on over underwear. Swimwear returns will only be accepted with the hygienic liner intact. Any personalized, monogrammed, altered or customized product is not eligible for return or exchange. Original shipping charges are not eligible for refund on orders that were shipped correctly.

Returns made for products over one year old may be accepted at the discretion of vineyard vines.

_Online and Retail Store Purchases:_

Proof of purchase can be established with a receipt or if we can find your transaction in your vineyard vines account.

_Full-price items with proof of purchase:_

  * Within 60 days of purchase: Full refund or merchandise credit
  * After 60 days of purchase: Merchandise credit of purchase value
  * After 90 days of purchase: Merchandise credit of last retail value

_Sale items with proof of purchase:_

  * Within 30 days of purchase: Full refund or merchandise credit
  * After 30 days of purchase: Merchandise credit of purchase value
  * After 60 days of purchase: Merchandise credit of last retail value

Without proof of purchase, returns will be processed and the customer will be issued merchandise credit of last retail value.

_Final Sale Items:_

All Clearance or Final Sale Items are not eligible for return, exchange, refund or credit.

_Items purchased with cash in store:_

Items purchased with cash at a retail store location and returned to our online fulfillment center with original receipt or packing slip will be refunded to a gift card. Retail locations will refund the purchase in the original form of payment.

_Outlet_

Merchandise purchased at vineyard vines outlet locations may be eligible for return, exchange, refund or merchandise credit within 30 days of purchase.

Merchandise must be returned in its original condition.

Returns must be accompanied by the original receipt.

All Clearance or Final Sale Items are not eligible for return, exchange, refund or credit.

Merchandise purchased at an outlet store cannot be returned to a retail store or to our online fulfillment center.

_Whalehouse and Sample Sales_

Merchandise purchased at a Whalehouse or Sample Sale is FINAL SALE. Returns or exchanges are not accepted. 

_Faulty Items_

Items are classified as faulty if they are not of standard quality or as described. Please note that items which are damaged as a result of normal wear and tear, by accident, or through misuse will not be considered faulty or accepted for return. 

_Purchase Information_

When returning your item(s), providing your receipt or order number helps us to locate your purchase. If you return your items without a receipt, we will need additional information to help you with your return. Please note this may add additional time for us to process your return. To return items in stores, you must present a receipt. 

_Gift Returns_

We would be more than happy to help you return your gift. Returns with Gift Receipt are eligible for return, exchange, refund or merchandise credit. 

_Online Exchanges_

To ensure that the item you want to exchange for is available, please place a new order online. Once we receive your return, we will refund the purchase to the original form of payment.

_Frequent Return Activity_

We offer a generous return policy for our customers. However, customers returning items repeatedly or in bulk may be refused at our discretion.

_International Returns Policy_

Borderfree allows us to deliver our items to our international customers. When returning an international order you will be credited by Borderfree in the same currency and using the same exchange rate as your original tender. Returns must be made within 180 days of purchase.

All European Union customers have a right to back out of a purchase within 7 days of completing the transaction (e.g. placing the order on the website). If a European Union customer cancels their order during this 7-day period, Borderfree will reimburse the customer for the cost of the product(s) AND any extra fees (i.e. shipping) paid by the customer to receive the item. Borderfree can, however, charge the customer for cost of shipping goods back to Borderfree. Reimbursement by Borderfree will be within 30 days.

vineyard vines reserves the right to review and modify this return policy from time to time at its discretion.

To exchange your product, give us a call at 800-892-4982 and we will do our best to get your new products out to you quickly! You will be charged for the merchandise on its way to you (shipping is on us, of course), and you’ll be credited for your original purchase as soon as we receive your return.

If you're looking to exchange a gift or store purchase, please complete the online form here. Please note that if the total value of your exchange is less than the value of the returned item(s), we will refund you the difference according to our return policies. If the total value of your exchange is greater than the value of the returned item(s), please include your contact information in the form below so we can contact you regarding proper form of payment. Please keep a copy of the label, exchange form, and any receipts or paperwork included with your exchange request.

How to exchange merchandise by mail:

  1. Complete the return section on the front side of this receipt and indicate items being returned
  2. Don't forget to let us know the reason for the returned item (please refer to our list of reason codes).
  3. Provide the product information for each new item you would like in the exchange form below.
  4. If the item you are returning is a gift, please fill out the contact information provided below.
  5. If the total value of your exchange is less than the value of the returned item(s), we will refund you the difference according to our return policies.
  6. If the total value of your exchange is greater than the value of the returned item(s), please include your contact information in the form below so we can contact you regarding proper form of payment.
  7. Take note of the tracking number for your records so that you can follow your shipment’s progress.

During high-volume seasons (holidays and Whale of a Sale, for example) it may take up to 30 days for your exchange to be processed. Should you need to expedite your exchange, we recommend that you purchase your new items from our website and then send the unwanted or incorrect items back to us for a refund. (To be eligible for an expedited exchange, you must be the original purchaser—we are only able to process a refund to the original form of payment).

We ask for up to 30 business days to process returns and exchanges from when they're received at our warehouse. Should you need to expedite your exchange, we recommend that you purchase your new items from our website and then send the unwanted or incorrect items back to us for a refund using a prepaid return label generated [here](https://www.vineyardvines.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-Vineyard-Vines-Site/default/OrderLocator-LoadOrderLocator). To be eligible for an expedited exchange, you must be the original purchaser—we are only able to process a refund to the original form of payment. 

All sales of Gift Cards are final and are not eligible for exchanges.

vineyard vines will honor a one-time price adjustment within 10 days of your order's shipment date.

Purchases made with any type of offer/promotion are not eligible for price adjustment, that includes but not limited to Flash Sales, Friends & Family and Whale of a Sale.

To receive a price adjustment, please contact one of our Customer Care representatives at 800-892-4982 or email: [tieguys@vineyardvines.com](mailto:tieguys@vineyardvines.com). Be sure to have your order number handy (this is found on your packing slip or in your order confirmation email.)

## Items, Sizes & Care

If you are writing to request a sticker, please note that all sticker requests must be mailed to the address below with a pre-addressed, postage-paid envelope. 

Vineyard vines sticker request  
181 harbor drive  
Stamford, CT 06901

To find out when a product will be back on the shelves, please call 800-892-4982. Also, please check back on the site regularly, you never know when your size or color choice may pop up!

We offer our products at vineyard vines stores, vineyard vines outlet stores and select retail stores throughout the country. Use [our store locator](https://www.vineyardvines.com/stores) to find the closest store to you.

Yes! You can select a complementary gift package for each item at checkout.

If you are ordering a Gift Card, please note this will come in a vineyard vines card holder.

Our ties come with a complementary gift box.

Note: Gift boxes will not be available during Whale of a Sale

Check out our [ size charts](https://www.vineyardvines.com/sizechart) to help determine what will work best for you and/or your loved ones.

Please find more information about sizing in our [size charts](https://www.vineyardvines.com/sizechart).

Our [boys’ ties](https://www.vineyardvines.com/silk-ties/boys-printed-ties/) are generally geared toward young men 5 feet tall and under.

The best method we’ve found is simply spot cleaning as necessary. You can also take your tote to the dry cleaner, but be sure to point out the silk trim.

## Payment Options, Gift Cards & Discounts

  * Visa
  * American Express
  * MasterCard
  * Discover Card
  * China UnionPay
  * PayPal
  * Amazon Pay
  * vineyard vines Gift Cards
  * Additional international payment methods displayed at checkout, where applicable

vineyard vines does not accept cash, checks or money orders for online purchases.

vineyard vines charges sales tax in the following states: AL, AR, CA, CT, DC, DE, FL, GA, IA, IL, IN, KS, KY, LA, ME, MD, MA, MI, MN, MS, MO, NV, NJ, NM, NY, NC, OH, OK, PA, SC, TN, TX, VT, VA, WA

No, you are not charged until your order ships. An initial authorization will be posted to your card but no funds are taken until your items are on their way! Please note, sometimes orders are shipped in multiple packages and this might cause multiple, smaller posts on your bank statement for your single order.

There are three ways to purchase a vineyard vines Gift Card: Applies to US addresses/customers only

  * By phone by calling 800-892-4982
  * At any of our retail locations

Our [ Gift Cards can be purchased online](https://www.vineyardvines.com/giftcards) or in stores. We also offer [e-Gift Cards](https://www.vineyardvines.com/egiftcards) that can be sent directly to the recipient over email. Our Gift Cards are available in increments from $25 - $500.

**Gift Cards:**  
Delivered in just a few days, our Gift Cards can be used at any of our stores or online. Your shipping options include Ground, UPS 2nd Day Air and UPS Next Day Air. Our Gift Cards come packed in a Gift Card holder.

**e-Gift Cards:**  
Need the good life in a hurry? [Send an e-Gift Card](https://www.vineyardvines.com/egiftcards)! The recipient will receive a vineyard vines e-Gift Card by email with a personalized message from you.

Our Gift Cards can be redeemed on vineyardvines.com, over the phone (800-892-4982), in vineyard vines retail stores, and vineyard vines outlet stores.

Unfortunately, vineyard vines is unable to reissue Gift Cards that have been lost or stolen.

No, vineyard vines Gift Cards cannot be reloaded.

Purchase a new vineyard vines [Gift Card](https://www.vineyardvines.com/giftcards) or [E-Gift Card](https://www.vineyardvines.com/egiftcards).

Read all our [Terms & Conditions](https://www.vineyardvines.com/terms/terms.html).

If you have any other questions regarding Gift Cards, please call our customer care team at 800-892-4982.

Just so you know…

You may come across vineyard vines coupon codes, discount codes and promotions on other websites but please note that these codes are generally not valid. Your best bet for being the first to know about sales and other promotions is to sign up for our email. 

Please read the fine print associated with any offer because they do sometimes change. Here are the standard exclusions Offer excludes: Gift cards, The Kentucky Derby Collection, personalization fees, Jim Nantz Forget Me Knot Collection, any charitable products, Yeti, Titleist® golf products, Costa sunglasses, Seabags, Smathers and Branson, Corksicle, Fat Boy, local store collections and any third party branded products.. No price adjustments will be made to prior purchases. Purchases made with this offer are not eligible for future price adjustment. Cannot be combined with any other offer. vineyard vines reserves the right to change or cancel this promotion at any time. Limit one discount per order. Use of this promotion constitutes acceptance of these terms and conditions, except where prohibited by law. Discount applies to merchandise only and not shipping & handling, taxes, or packaging. 

vineyard vines believes your brain is a terrible thing to waste 

College students ONLY. 

**How do I get our student discount on vineyardvines.com?**

  *   * Click[ here](https://www.vineyardvines.com/student-discount/student-discount.html) to see if you’re eligible with SheerID on our site

**How do I get our student discount at a vineyard vines store?**

Show one of our crew members your student ID when you’re checking out, and he or she will apply your discount! 

Terms and Conditions 

*Offer valid online at vineyardvines.com and at participating retail stores. Student discount offered all year at our retail locations. Discount is not valid at vineyard vines outlet locations. Code is valid for one-time use online, or card must be presented in store at checkout. Valid on full-price merchandise only. Cannot be combined with any other offer. vineyard vines reserves the right to change or cancel this promotion at any time. Offer excludes gift cards, Yeti coolers, Titleist®, Costa sunglasses, monogramming & personalization, special collections, and all other third-party products. No price adjustments will be made on previous purchases. Purchases made with this offer are not eligible for future price adjustments. Use of this promotion constitutes acceptance of these terms and conditions, except where prohibited by law. Discount applies to merchandise only and not shipping & handling, taxes, or packaging. 

We offer teachers a 15% discount at vineyard vines retail stores. Teachers must show a valid ID at checkout to receive this discount.

vineyard vines is proud to stand by our brave servicemen and servicewomen. 

Active, veteran, retired, and reservist US Army, Navy, Air Force, Marines, and Coast Guard personnel, and spouses/dependents of active personnel, are eligible to receive a 15% vineyard vines military discount on vineyardvines.com and at participating vineyard vines retail stores in the United States (not in vineyard vines outlets/whalehouse sales) 

**How do I get the military discount on vineyardvines.com?**

  * Click[ here](https://www.vineyardvines.com/military-discount/military-discount.html) to see if you’re eligible with SheerID on our site

**How do I get the military discount at a vineyard vines store?**

Show one of our crewmembers your military ID when you’re checking out, and he or she will apply your discount! 

**Terms and Conditions**

*Our military discount is offer valid online at vineyardvines.com and at participating retail stores. Discount is not valid at vineyard vines outlet locations. Proper identification must be shown. Code is valid for one-time use online, or card must be presented in store at checkout. Valid on full-price merchandise only. Cannot be combined with any other offer. vineyard vines reserves the right to change or cancel this promotion at any time. Offer excludes gift cards, Yeti coolers, Titleist®, Costa sunglasses, monogramming & personalization, special collections, and all other third-party products. No price adjustments will be made on previous purchases. Purchases made with this offer are not eligible for future price adjustments. Use of this promotion constitutes acceptance of these terms and conditions, except where prohibited by law. Discount applies to merchandise only and not shipping & handling, taxes, or packaging. 

## Registering & My Account

Nope! You can check out as a guest, and if you change your mind, you can always register at the end of the checkout process.

When you order from vineyard vines in the future, we’ll remember your information such as billing and shipping addresses to ensure a quicker checkout next time around. You can also store other information, access your order history, and manage your email preferences.

Yes. The security of your information is very important to us. We use 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. SSL technology encrypts your order information to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than vineyard vines. Read more about secure mode.

Yes, you will automatically be added to our mailing lists. You can unsubscribe to vineyard vines emails in your account at any time.

If you would like to be removed from our catalog mailing list, please email [ catalog@vineyardvines.com](mailto:catalog@vineyardvines.com) with the phrase "no catalog" in the subject line and your name and your complete mailing address in the body of the email.

If you give us your email address either on the home page, when you register, or order, we will send you emails about events, new arrivals, and promotions that we feel will be of interest to you. To be removed from our email list, simply [log in to My Account](https://www.vineyardvines.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-Vineyard-Vines-Site/default/Login-ShowDialog?reqt=unsecure) and opt out of our email promotions.

When you supply your postal address either when requesting a free catalog or placing an order, you will receive the vineyard vines catalog by mail. If you choose to give us your telephone number on the order form, it is for the purpose of contacting you regarding your order. We will not call you regarding promotions or just to chat if we get bored.

If you do not want a vineyard vines catalog, please send us an email to [ catalog@vineyardvines.com](mailto:catalog@vineyardvines.com) with the following:

  * The phrase "no catalog" in the subject line
  * Your name and your complete mailing address

You can edit or delete your email or postal address at anytime through the [My Account](https://www.vineyardvines.com/account) Page.

If you forget your password, you can [request that it be emailed](https://www.vineyardvines.com/resetpassword) to your email address. We will not give passwords out over the phone, nor will we email them to a different email address than the one used to register.

Please note: If you request to have your password emailed to you, your credit card information will be deleted from your profile.

## Connect with Us

Yes! You can get the Good Life… on the go! Download the vineyard vines [iPhone app](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/vineyard-vines/id1047812991) and  iPad app  in the Apple App Store, and our [Android app](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.vineyardvines.android&hl=en) in the Google Play store.

We sure do! Connect with us here:

In addition to supporting the causes we believe in, we also feel strongly about contributing to the charitable efforts of our customers and their communities. As a dear friend once told us: "Give back more to the community than you receive." Not only do we live by this philosophy, we’ve built our entire company around it, too. [Download our guidelines and donation form](https://demandware.edgesuite.net/aahw_prd/on/demandware.static/-/Sites-Vineyard-Vines-Library/default/dwc4dff0db/Donation%20Request%20Form.pdf) (PDF).  

## Privacy & Security

PRIVACY POLICY UPDATED January 2019

At vineyardvines.com, your privacy is a top priority. Please read our privacy policy details. We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining and using this information responsibly. This privacy policy addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our website as well as information we collect directly from customers on the telephone or in our stores (the “Sites”) in accordance with applicable privacy laws including, where applicable, the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and other UK and European data privacy laws and applicable US privacy laws (the “Privacy Laws”).

vineyard vines® collects customer information to improve your overall shopping experience with us. We collect your personal information to fulfill our contractual obligations, our statutory obligations and/or the legitimate interests of vineyard vines and for other purposes for which vineyard vines has a lawful basis under the Privacy Laws. 

In addition, vineyard vines may, and only with your consent, process your personal information in order to communicate with you for marketing purposes. In this event, we may provide additional information that we believe may be of interest, including about offers, promotions, and news updates. You have the right to unsubscribe when you have provided consent to receive these communications by emailing [privacy@vineyardvines.com](mailto:privacy@vineyardvines.com) or by following the instructions in any such communication, e.g. by clicking on the link to unsubscribe.

By using the Sites, you signify your acceptance of the privacy policy as amended from time to time. 

Personal information relating to you and your order history are only available to you if you provide the correct password that you create on vineyardvines.com. After providing your password, you can edit or delete your information at any time through the My Account page.

If you forget your password, you can select the “forgot your password?” link on the login screen and we will send you an email (to the email address that you used to register your account) including a link that will enable you to reset your password. We will not give passwords out over the phone or by email. 

Your address book, located in the shipping addresses & contacts page, is your personal storage space. We do not use the names of the people in your address book to send email promotions or catalogs by mail.

If you are visiting vineyardvines.com from a location outside of the United States, you will be connected through and to servers located within the United States (where data privacy laws are less stringent than in the European Union and some other jurisdictions). Some of the recipients of your personal information as specified above may be located in countries (including the United States) that do not provide a level of data protection equivalent to that set forth by the European Union and some other jurisdictions. vineyard vines will take appropriate steps to ensure that such recipients act in accordance with the Privacy Laws. If you choose to access or use the Sites, you consent to the transfer, use and disclosure of information in accordance with this privacy policy and subject to the Privacy Laws. All vineyardvines.com orders will be accepted and fully processed in and shipped from the United States and all information you provide will be securely maintained in our Web server and internal systems located within the United States.

Purchases made through our website that ship outside of the United States are made through Borderfree, Inc. (“Borderfree”), not vineyard vines. Personal information that you provide in connection with web orders that ship outside of the United States is provided to Borderfree, not vineyard vines, though Borderfree may share this information with us. You can view Borderfree’s privacy policy at [ https://www.borderfree.com/privacy/en_us/ ](https://www.borderfree.com/privacy/en_us/) for more information on their privacy practices. 

Any personal information you provide to us on the Sites when you register or update an account, participate in a contest, sweepstakes, promotion or survey, join our mailing list, request a catalog, shop online, shop by telephone or in our stores, or request information (i.e. name, address, email address, telephone number and credit card information) is maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems.

With your consent, we may occasionally share our postal and email lists, as well as your shopping history (but not your credit card information), with third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you and who have their own privacy policy in place. If at any time you do not want us to share your personal information with these third parties, you may opt-out by emailing us at [privacy@vineyardvines.com](mailto:privacy@vineyardvines.com). Please include your name and postal address and write "do not share my information" in the subject line. You may also opt-out by writing to us at the address located at the end of this privacy policy and including your name, postal and email address.

We also may share your information with unaffiliated third parties who provide services to vineyard vines such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our website, conduct promotions or surveys, order fulfillment, etc. vineyard vines does not authorize any of these service providers to use or disclose customer information other than in connection with providing services to vineyard vines.

In the event of a sale or merger of vineyard vines our customer's personal information may be shared with the merged or purchasing entity. You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if required to do so by law, governmental request or court order or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court order or to protect the users of our website or the public.

We may share personal information with other group entities for any of the purposes set out above. Our group entities, in turn, are not permitted to share personal information with other non-affiliated entities, except as described herein or otherwise permitted by the Privacy Laws or other applicable laws. 

Where personal information is processed by third parties outside the UK and EEA, we will ensure appropriate safeguards are in place to adequately protect it, as required by applicable law. 

To enhance your shopping experience, the Sites may have links to other sites. Those Web sites will have their own policies on privacy that you may wish to review. vineyard vines has no responsibility for these linked Web sites.

We use cookies to recognize you and your preferences to make shopping easier and provide you with a customized experience on our website. Cookies are bits of information that we automatically store on your computer if your computer accepts cookies. vineyard vines places a unique user ID number on your cookie which allows us to access information that will improve your shopping experience - such as holding items in your shopping bag, accessing your address book, or providing you with customized pages based on your past viewing or purchasing preferences. We also use cookies to track traffic to different parts of the website in order to make improvements and optimize your shopping experience, as well as for remarketing purposes to serve you with internet advertisements (as more fully discussed in the Advertising section below). 

We use marketing technologies to help us maintain and analyze our data and allow us to market more efficiently. They may use cookies or web beacons to collect information about you, in connection with providing you information via email, Internet ads or direct mail about products and services that might be of interest to you. 

If you do not wish to have a cookie on your system, you can set your browser preferences to refuse them. In order to disable cookies, please consult your browser's help section for instructions.

We participate in interest-based or behavioral advertising. This means that you may receive communications, special promotions, and see advertising on the Sites or other websites tailored to how you browse or shop at our stores, on the Sites or other websites. You may also see advertising for Vineyard Vines on other advertising on other websites based on your particular interests and online activity on the Sites or other websites. You have the choice to tell us not to collect and use this information. Learn more about this kind of advertising and how you can opt out by clicking here:[www.networkadvertising.org/choices](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices).

vineyard vines may use Adobe and the third-party cookie DoubleClick to optimize our Sites based on the traffic we receive and assist with marketing. To learn more about Adobe, including options for opting out and/or managing the ads you may see online please visit:[ http://www.adobe.com/privacy.html](https://www.adobe.com/privacy.html).

Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) has not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals and therefore, vineyard vines and the Sites do not recognize DNT.  

If you give us your email address either on the footer of our website or when you register, or order, we will send you emails about promotions. To remove yourself from our email list you may click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails and follow the instructions to opt out of future email communications. When you supply your postal address either when requesting a free catalog or placing an order, you will receive the vineyard vines catalog by mail. If you choose to give us your telephone number on the order form, it is for the purpose of contacting you regarding your order. We will not call you regarding promotions. If you do not want a vineyard vines catalog, please send us an email to: catalog@vineyardvines.com  with the following:

  * The phrase "no catalog" in the subject line

  * Your name and your complete mailing address

**Updating email or postal addresses**

You can edit your email address or edit/delete your postal address at anytime through the My Account Page.

vineyard vines® is concerned about the privacy of young children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13 (or such higher age as required by applicable law). vineyard vines® does not sell products for purchase by children, and all children's products we sell are for purchase by adults only. If vineyard vines learns that a child under the age of 13 (or such higher age as required by applicable law) has submitted personally identifiable information online without parental consent, it will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required or allowed by law). If you become aware of any personally identifiable information we have collected from children under 13 (or such higher age as required by applicable law), please contact us at [tieguys@vineyardvines.com](mailto:tieguys@vineyardvines.com) or by calling 1-800-892-4982. 

The security of your information is very important to us. We use industry-standard security techniques to help protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected from you at the Sites. When you access your account information or transmit personally identifiable data to the Sites, that information is stored on servers that the Sites have attempted to secure from unauthorized access or intrusion. We use the 256-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. SSL technology encrypts your order information to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than vineyard vines®

Once you land on any page of our website, your computer will begin communicating with our server in secure mode. You can tell that you are in secure mode by the following:

  * The "http" in the web address will be replaced by "https"
  * You you will see padlock depending on the browser (Microsoft Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari.)
  * Only browsers that use the 256-bit Secure Socket Layer technology are able to order through the Vineyard Vines web site. If your browser does not support SSL, you can update your browser.

While we implement these and other security measures on this site, please note that 100% security is not always possible.

Customers who are California residents may request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email us at [privacy@vineyardvines.com](mailto:privacy@vineyardvines.com) and write "California Privacy Rights" in the subject line. Alternatively, you may write to us at the address located and the end of this privacy policy.

Customers who reside in the UK or in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) have certain rights relating to the personal information we hold in accordance with and subject to the Privacy Laws to: (i) check whether we hold personal information about you and to access such data (in accordance with our policy); (ii) request the correction of personal information about you that is inaccurate; (iii) have a copy of the personal information we hold about you provided to you or another controller where technically feasible; (iv) request the erasure of your personal information; and (v) request the restriction of processing concerning you. To do so, please send your request to [privacy@vineyardvines.com](mailto:privacy@vineyardvines.com) and write “EU Privacy Rights”.

Customers may make a complaint in accordance with applicable Privacy Laws to a supervisory authority. 

vineyard vines will retain your personal information only for as long as is reasonably necessary to achieve the purposes for which it is collected. Thereafter, we will delete (or otherwise erase, de-identify or pseudonymise or equivalent) any such personal data except as required or permitted by applicable law or regulation. 

vineyard vines is dedicated to making its website usable and available to everyone out there living the Good Life by always meeting or exceeding the requirements of the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines 2.0.

Every year, we work with a consultant to make our website better for everyone. We’ve had all of our pages and our site’s functionality reviewed by this consultant and implemented all suggestions we can. We’ve also had our third-party services and features audited, and they’ve implemented several of the changes we’ve requested.

If you have any questions about our compliance, or any questions at all, call us at 1.800.892.4982 or email us at [tieguys@vineyardvines.com](mailto:tieguys@vineyardvines.com?subject=Accessibility)

vineyard vines may update our privacy policy from time to time and use of the information we collect now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of use. Whenever we make a change, we will post the updated policy at this site and we encourage you to check our policy periodically. By using our website following the posting of a change in the privacy policy, you consent to the updated policy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us:

Email: [tieguys@vineyardvines.com](mailto:tieguys@vineyardvines.com)  
Phone: 1-800-892-4982  
Fax: 1-800-892-3606  
Mail: vineyard vines  
Customer Care  
181 Harbor Drive  
Stamford, CT 06902

**IMPORTANT:** The “Dispute Resolution and Arbitration” section below requires you to arbitrate claims you may have against vineyard vines, meaning you cannot bring claims against vineyard vines in court, and confirms your agreement to a class action waiver in arbitration. It affects your legal rights. Please read it carefully.

**What are vineyard vines mobile messages?**

vineyard vines mobile messages are recurring SMS text messages that contain promotional alerts, such as a coupon for 15% off your next vineyard vines purchase, or notice when an out-of-stock product becomes available. You will only receive vineyard vines mobile messages if you have opted in to receive them. Frequency of SMS text messages may vary. 

**How do I sign up for vineyard vines mobile messages?**

You can sign up for vineyard vines mobile messages by texting VINEYARD or other keywords provided by vineyard vines (the “short code”) to 74886. Reply Y when prompted to confirm subscription. You can still receive vineyard vines goods and services even if you do not agree to receive, or opt out of receiving, vineyard vines mobile messages. 

**Is it free?**

Although all vineyard vines mobile messages are complimentary, message and data rates may apply. Depending on your SMS message plan, your carrier may charge you for each message you send and receive. 

**What if I don’t want to receive any more messages?**

To stop receiving all vineyard vines mobile messages, simply text STOP in reply to a text message or to the short code 74886. You may will receive one final message confirming your opt-out. You can always opt back in. Additionally, please let us know if you change or deactivate your mobile number. 

**What if I want more info?**

To request more info, simply text HELP to the short code 74886, email [tieguys@vineyardvines.com](mailto:tieguys@vineyardvines.com), or call us toll-free at 1-800-892-4982. 

**What are the participating carriers?**

Most wireless carriers support vineyard vines mobile messages, although various factors, including your equipment and weather, affect your ability to send a receive SMS messages. Mobile carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. Check with your wireless carrier if you have questions. 

**How are the messages sent?**

We may use autodialer or non-autodialer technology to send vineyard vines mobile messages to your mobile phone number that you used to opt in. 

**Privacy Notice and Additional Terms**

The vineyard vines Privacy Policy, available [here](https://www.vineyardvines.com/frequently-asked-questions/frequently-asked-questions.html#privacy), applies to your participation in a mobile messaging program. 

**Dispute Resolution and Arbitration**

**Please read this section carefully. It affects your legal rights, including your right to file a lawsuit in court.**

Mandatory, Bilateral Arbitration. BY OPTING INTO A MOBILE MESSAGING PROGRAM, YOU AND VINEYARD VINES AGREE TO RESOLVE ANY DISPUTE ARISING OUT OF, OR RELATING TO, VINEYARD VINES MOBILE MESSAGES, EXCEPT FOR DISPUTES THAT QUALIFY FOR SMALL CLAIMS COURT, BY FINAL AND BINDING, BILATERAL ARBITRATION BEFORE A NEUTRAL ARBITRATOR INSTEAD OF IN A COURT BY A JUDGE OR JURY. YOU ALSO AGREE THAT VINEYARD VINES AND YOU ARE EACH WAIVING THE RIGHT TO SUE IN COURT AND TO HAVE A TRIAL BY JURY. YOU AGREE THAT ANY ARBITRATION WILL TAKE PLACE ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS; CLASS ARBITRATIONS AND CLASS ACTIONS ARE NOT PERMITTED AND YOU ARE AGREEING TO GIVE UP THE ABILITY TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION. This agreement to arbitrate is intended to be broadly interpreted, and expressly includes claims brought under the Telephone Consumer Protection Act, 47 U.S.C. § 227, or any other statute, regulation, or legal or equitable theory.

  * **Arbitration Rules**

Notwithstanding your and vineyard vines’ agreement that Missouri law governs interpretation and application of these terms generally, you further hereby agree that the Federal Arbitration Act, 9 U.S.C. § 1, et seq., applies to this agreement to arbitrate, and governs all questions of whether a dispute is subject to arbitration. 

Unless you and vineyard vines agree otherwise in writing, the arbitration shall be administered by Judicial Arbitration and Mediation Services, Inc. (“JAMS”), pursuant to [JAMS Streamlined Arbitration Rules and Procedures](https://www.vineyardvines.com/on/demandware.static/-/Sites-Vineyard-Vines-Library/default/dw95f8c825/JAMS_streamlined_arbitration_rules-2014.pdf) (“JAMS Streamlined Rules”), as modified by this agreement, and consistent with [JAMS Policy on Consumer Arbitrations Pursuant to Pre-Dispute Clauses Minimum Standards of Procedural Fairness](https://www.jamsadr.com/consumer-minimum-standards/) (“JAMS Consumer Fairness Standards”). Notwithstanding JAMS Streamlined Rule 8(b), you and vineyard vines agree that any dispute as to the arbitrability of a claim brought by either you or vineyard vines shall be resolved by a court of competent jurisdiction. 

  * **The Arbitrator’s Decision**

The arbitrator will conduct hearings, if any, by teleconference or videoconference, rather than by personal appearances, unless the arbitrator determines upon request by you or by us that an in-person hearing is appropriate. Any in-person appearances will be held at a location which is reasonably convenient to both parties with due consideration of their ability to travel and other pertinent circumstances. If the parties are unable to agree on a location, such determination should be made by JAMS or by the arbitrator. 

The arbitrator’s decision will follow the terms of these Terms and Conditions, will consist of a written statement stating the disposition of each claim, will be final and binding, and will include the essential findings and conclusions upon which the arbitrator based the award. The arbitrator will have authority to award temporary, interim, or permanent injunctive relief or relief providing for specific performance of these Terms and Conditions, but only to the extent necessary to provide relief warranted by the claimant’s individual claim. Judgment on the arbitration award may be entered in any court with jurisdiction. If you prevail in arbitration, you will be entitled to an award of attorneys’ fees and expenses, to the extent provided under applicable law. Notwithstanding any of the foregoing, nothing in these Terms and Conditions will preclude you from bringing issues to the attention of federal, state, or local agencies, and, if the law allows, they can seek relief against us for you. 

Email: [tieguys@vineyardvines.com](mailto:tieguys@vineyardvines.com)  
Phone: 1-800-892-4982  
Fax: 1-800-892-3606  
Mail: vineyard vines  
Customer Care  
181 Harbor Drive  
Stamford, CT 06902
